propertyminder.com 2018-11-24

# Privacy Policy | IDX Websites for Real Estate, MLS integrated Realtor Websites, Custom IDX, lead capture, IDX websites with CRM, Client Relationship Management, Referral Marketing, Lead Capture Websites for Real Esate, Listing Generation for Realtors + Brokers

**PropertyMinder Privacy policy, 2017**

Your privacy is important to PropertyMinder and its client. This Privacy Policy outlines information that this website may collect and how that information may be used.

**Information Collected and Used**

This website does not collect personally identifiable information about visitors (e.g., name, address, telephone number, MLS information, credit card information or email address) unless you have submitted it. If you do not want your personal data collected, please do not submit it. Information you submit may be used to offer or provide products or services to you, communicate with you, collect fees and for other business purposes. Your personal information may be shared with or used by PropertyMinder, its client, service providers, vendors, financial institutions and government officials or others if required by law or litigation. Your information will be retained for as long as necessary to permit it to be used for the purposes described above and to comply with applicable law or regulations.

This website may automatically (i.e., not via registration) collect technical but not personally identifiable characteristics of computers and browsers visiting the site, and this information may be shared with others. Examples of this type of information include the Internet browser version and settings, the type of computer operating system and the referring domain name.

**Contacting You**

Information you submit on the website and through other sources may be used to tell you about products and services that might interest you or to invite you to participate in surveys, seminars and other events. E-mail messages will provide a method by which you may opt-out of future mailings. To indicate a preference to not receive e-mails or other communications, please send a message to support@propertyminder.com.

We may need to communicate with you regarding the usability of products or services or critical issues relating to them, such as subscription renewal notices, critical notices or legally mandated notices. Providing us with your phone number is optional. By submitting your telephone number, you are consenting to being contacted via telephone, even if your name appears on the Federal “Do-not-call List”.

**Information and data security**

Physical, electronic and managerial security procedures have been put in place to safeguard and secure the information collected by this website. However, PropertyMinder cannot guarantee that these security procedures will not be breached and PropertyMinder will not be liable if information that belongs to you is obtained or used by an unintended person.

**Links**

This website may contain links to other websites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of third-party websites.

**Policy Effective Date**

The privacy policy is effective as of August 20, 2007. This policy may be amended at any time by posting a revised version on the website. The revised version will be effective at the time it is posted.

**Feedback or concerns**

If you have any questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy, please email support@propertyminder.com or call toll free 1-800-743-5820.
